（忆往昔）
路西法本来是史上最可怕的怪物
Lucifer was the biggest monster ever hatched,
直到你跟我放出了更可怕的怪物
until you and I hatched one that's even worse.
我是原初 也将会是终结
I was the beginning, and I will be the end.
我会成为唯一
I will be all that there is.
可你在夺取他人性命
You're taking people's lives.
如果你反抗 天空中的每个天使
If you resist, each and every angel in the skies.
会毁灭你
will smite you.
你真的能打败她吗
Can you really beat her?
- 我可以 - 那么好
- I can. - Then, yes.
路西法
Lucifer.
见鬼
Bloody hell.
你呢 小狗狗
What about you, little puppy?
用你的舌头
Use your tongue.
「上帝之手」 一件超能武器
"The Hand of God" … a super weapon.
你觉得我们可以用它对付阿玛拉吗
Do you think we can use it against Amara?
这是什么
What is this?
亚伦之杖
The Rod of Aaron.
上帝之手
A Hand of God.
如果我们要对抗她 有什么武器
If we're gonna fight her, what better way to arm up.
比他残留的法力更好呢
than with an actual dose of his power?
没能量了
It's kicked.
没法力了吧
You're out of juice, huh?
我们没查到任何其他上帝之手的资料
We've got jack on another Hand of God,
救小卡的办法更是没找到
and we've got even less jack on how to save Cass.
如果他想被我们救的话
If he wants to be saved.
他当然想
He does…
（如今）
（沙特阿拉伯 内夫得沙漠）
他在哪
Where is he?
诺埃尔 你找我我就来了
Noel, I came when you asked.
你有点憔悴啊
You're looking a trifle peaky.
真的在你这儿吗
Do you truly have it?
给你了
And it's yours…
只要你能遵守约定
If you hold up your end of the bargin.
我这辈子过得不错
I've had a good life…
都要多谢你
thanks to you.
这世上没几个秘密没被我解开
Very few of the world's secrets I haven't cracked.
看来值得以灵魂交换了
It seemed worth a soul…
至少当时我那么觉得
at the time.
总是如此
It always does.
毁了那玩意
Destroy that thing.
先把东西给我看
Show me the object first.
羊角号
A shofar.
约书亚的号角 上帝曾用手碰过
The Horn of Joshua, touched by the hand of God.
小心
Easy.
小心哦
Easy there.
是真品
It's authentic.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
把那玩意撕毁
Now tear that thing up.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
我想我时日无多了
I don't think I have long.
你真有先见之明
How very prescient of you.
真业余
Amateurs.
[邪恶力量 第11季第18集]
你没听到吗
Are you not hearing me?
我说我手上有
I said I have in my possession.
我们共同问题的解决办法
the solution to our collective problems.
你该乐得跳起来
You should be doing a jig.
我不跳
I don't jig.
我怎么知道你真逃出了路西法的魔掌
Now, how do I know you even escaped Lucifer.
不是他逼你说这些话的
and he's not making you say all this?
真是的 你的愤世嫉俗令人郁闷
Honestly, you cynicism is depressing.
路西法为什么要逼我讨论
Why would Lucifer force me to discuss.
能毁掉他的东西
the very means of his destruction?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
一件武器 蕴含了神力
A weapon … one that channels divinity.
是的 有足够法力毁灭
Yes, powerful enough to help destroy.
黑暗那样的力量
a force like the Darkness…
或是路西法
or Lucifer.
你难道没有在寻找这样的东西吗
Tell me you haven't been searching for such a thing.
上帝之手吗 当然在找
A Hand of God? Of course we have.
我猜到了
Thought as much.
圣路易斯 比克曼街老邮局
St. Louis. The old post office on Beekman.
克劳力
Crowley.
萨姆
Sam!
我怎么知道这会好用
How do I know that any of this is working?
你说了那么多 我没觉得有什么不同
I don't feel any different, for all of your promises.
我警告你 你可别想捉弄我
I warn you, I'm not one to be trifled with.
[咒语]
暂时够了 小可怜
That's enough for now, poor wee thing,
但你会好起来的
but you're coming along.
我会像说好的那样治好你
I'll heal you just as I promised.
你是谁来着
And who are you again?
能连通自然力量
One who communes with the natural forces and.
以其帮助你这样
channels them to help the less fortunate,
可怜人的人
such as yourself.
是吗
Really?
你是他妈妈
You're his mother.
什么
Say what, dear?
克劳力叔叔的妈妈
Uncle Crowley's mother.
叔叔
Uncle?
我还小的时候 他曾试图控制我
He tried controlling me when I was a child.
是他派你来带我回去吗
Did he send you to bring me back?
老天 不是
Heavens, no.
我儿子和我讨厌彼此
My son and I loathe each other.
那你为什么要帮我
Then why are you helping me?
因为你会赢的 亲爱的
Because you're going to win, my dear.
是的 我知道你和你
Yes, I know about the grievance.
哥哥以及他的大天使之间的矛盾
between you and your brother and his archangel.
我跟路西法也有账要算
I have my own ax to grind with Lucifer.
你认识他
You know him?
认识
Know him?
但你没死
And yet, you live.
是啊
Aye.
就像你 我这人能大难不死
Like yourself, I'm a survivor.
艰辛的生活教会我要做足准备
A hard life has taught me to be prepared.
我早就在我身上
I, long ago, secreted within my person.
存留了一小点强大的魔法
a wee casket of powerful magic.
当我体内的咒语感应到我的生命力衰退时
When the spell inside me sensed my life-force ebbing…
它便开始起效
it went to work.
我复活了
And I was revived.
路西法现在在哪
Where is Lucifer now?
他躲了起来
He's hidden himself from me,
而我也有账要算
and I, too, have a score to settle.
不着急
All in good time.
现在 你还因讨厌的
Right now, you're still weak.
天使攻击而虚弱
from that pesky angel smiting.
你能治好我吗
And you can fix that?
是的 还不止
Aye, and so much more.
你可以毁灭你的敌人 我猜
You can destroy your enemies and, I imagine,
还能按你的意愿重塑这个世界
remake the world any way you choose.
我会陪在你身边
And I… will be by your side.
地方不错
Nice digs.
墓穴守卫不在啊
The Crypt Keeper out of town?
我还活着就算走运了
I'm lucky to be alive.
路西法把我像狗一样拴在我自己的宫殿里
Lucifer had me trussed up like a dog in my own palace.
「宫殿」
"Palace"?
那个废弃的疯人院啊
You mean the abandoned nuthouse.
他把我关在狗舍里
He kept me in a kennel!
他还让他的恶魔
And he turned all his demons …
我的恶魔 与我反目
my demons … against me.
他们日夜不停地到处找我 想杀我
They scour the earth, day and night, looking to kill me.
必须得解决他
He has to be dealt with.
你叫我们来就为这个
So is this why you brought us here?
跟路西法赌气
Some lousy grudge match with Lucifer?
是啊 你说的那个上帝之手在哪
Yeah, where's this, uh, Hand of God you were talking about?
我就要说到了
I'm getting to that.
你们制服阿玛拉的唯一希望
Your only hope of subduing Amara.
就是拥有与她相当的力量
is to match the level of power that she possesses.
可不是呢 继续说
No kidding. And?
我有约书亚的号角
And I have the Horn of Joshua.
约书亚
Joshua.
打败了耶律哥的那个吗
As in the Joshua that won the battle of Jericho.
我愿意将它交给你们
And I'm willing to entrust it to your capable hands.
怎么了 我刚说愿把那东西给你们了
What? I just said I'd give you the thing.
- 条件呢 - 条件呢
- If? - If?
你们就这么说「谢谢」吗
Is this how you say "Thank you"?
你觉得这玩意都长树上的吗
You think these things grow on bloody trees?!
少扯淡了 克劳力
Cut the crap, Crowley.
你总会提条件的
With you, there's always an "If".
好吧
Fine.
我可以把号角给你们
I will give you the Horn.
但你们得帮忙把路西法从小卡的皮囊中驱逐出去
if you help me exorcise Lucifer from Castiel's vessel.
然后马上把他关回笼子
and then return him immediately to the Cage.
就这样吗
That's all?
好吧
Okay.
号角在哪呢
And where is this horn?
- 当然是安全地藏好了 - 嗯
- Safely hidden, naturally. - Yeah.
克劳力 就算我们能把路西法
Crowley, even if we could exorcise.
从小卡体内驱逐出去
Lucifer out of Cass,
笼子几乎无法闯入
the Cage is damn near impenetrable.
是靠《诅咒之书》里的咒语才把路西法弄了出来
It took a spell from the Book of the Damned to spring Lucifer,
罗威娜又把书藏起来了
and Rowena hid the book.
而且我们需要书加上她 才有一线希望
And we would need both the book and her to even have a shot.
我有说这事会很简单了吗
Did I say this would be easy?
没有
No. I did not.
你知道罗威娜在哪吗
Do you even know where Rowena is?
在哪发霉吧
Rotting somewhere, I assume.
路西法扭断了她的脖子
Lucifer snapped her neck.
路西法
Lucifer.
乔菲尔
Jofiel.
你怎么样了
How's it hangin'?
别激动
Easy, there.
真完美
So perfect.
卡西迪奥 天堂头号通缉犯
Castiel, one of heaven's most wanted,
被天堂第一公敌附身了
possessed by heaven's most hated.
我没有恶意
I come in peace.
我只想再次加入大家的行动
I just want to be a part of the action again.
我想帮把手
I want to lend a hand.
兄弟们
Brothers!
好了 各位
Okay, guys.
想合击杀黑暗没有成功啊
So, trying to smite the Darkness was a bust, huh?
你们有整个天堂的力量支持
You had all of the power of heaven behind you.
却还是无法拖慢她一点
Couldn't even slow the bitch down.
不必觉得自己像个废物
Well, no need to feel like abject losers.
你们吸取了宝贵教训
You learned a valuable lesson here.
你们需要我
You need me.
好吧
All right.
没有充满敬畏
Not giddy with awe.
你
You…
把乔菲尔弄爆了
exploded Jofiel.
或许是乔菲尔自爆了呢
Or did Jofiel explode himself?
随口一说
Just sayin'.
上帝把你驱逐出了天堂
God cast you out of heaven.
你以为是谁到处散播这条小报新闻的
And who do you think spread that tabloid headline?
是G船长 永生者
It was Captain G, the Eternal One.
为什么呢
And why?
因为我不肯
Because I didn't buy in.
像他一样 对人类有执迷的爱
to his obsessive-compulsive love for mankind.
人类是他的创造物
Mankind is his creation.
拜托
Come on!
他又不是发明了普锐斯
It's not like he invented the Prius,
那车还挺不错呢
which actually works.
我不用告诉你们人类是多么完蛋
I don't have to tell you people what a mess mankind is.
塞勒姆女巫审判
The Salem Witch Trials…
第三帝国
…Third Reich…
双子塔
…Twin Towers.
是啊 偶尔
And, sure, every once in a while,
他会降临个瘟疫 教训他们一番
He'll send down a little plague to straighten them out,
但从不是根本的办法
but it's nothing permanent.
人类创造了广岛 然后又毁掉重建
Humanity brought us Hiroshima and got a redo.
我只是质疑了他对轻重的判断
I merely questioned His priorities,
就被踢走了
and I got the boot.
他说你是邪恶的
He said you're evil.
化身
Incarnate.
邪恶的化身
E-Evil incarnate.
那是营销
It's marketing.
他是在消费者心里埋下了需求
He's creating a need in the consumer's mind.
如果没有超级坏蛋 就没有超级救星
Can't be a Super Savior if you don't have a Super Villain.
你有什么提议
So, what are you offering?
解决这窘境的办法
Well, a way out of this pickle.
「窘境」是指黑暗
By "pickle, " you mean the Darkness.
你能跟她讲理吗
You can reason with her?
这恐怕不行
Well…I doubt that.
但我可以把她关起来
But I can lock her away.
这次是永远关起来
This time for good.
我以前也干过的
Done it before.
这事老爸没说吗
Pops didn't tell you that, huh?
那你
Once you've…
干掉她之后
gotten rid of her,
你会
you'll want…
想
to…
留下吗
stay around?
我喜欢你的想法
Oh, I like the way you think.
我好激动
Man, am I jazzed!
如果你们愿意
If it makes you comfy,
可以叫我上帝
could call me God.
等等
Hold on, okay?
我们先倒回来
Let's just put it in reverse.
我们会把路西法关回笼子的
We will put Lucifer back in the Cage.
但要先把阿玛拉关起来
after we put Amara back on ice.
必须是这个先后顺序 否则路西法
It has to happen in that order, otherwise there is no Lucifer,
笼子 一切都要消失了
there's no Cage, there's no nothing.
他多年来一直恨着我们
He's spent years marinating in hate against us!
必须除掉他
He has to go.
问题是 我们可能需要他
Problem is, we may need him.
他跟阿玛拉斗过
He's been down this road with Amara before.
他或许是唯一有能力
He might be the only one powerful enough.
使用号角对付她的人
to use the Horn against her.
他让我清洁地板
He had me cleaning the floors.
用舌头舔
with my tongue!
他喊我「狗狗」
He called me "puppy"!
他逼我求他
He made me beg!
好了 得了
All right. Come on.
你是为这个吗
Is this what this is about?
你的破自尊心
Your stupid ego?
就因为他当着一群小破恶魔的面羞辱了你
The fact that he dissed you in front of a bunch of stupid demons?
你没那么笨的 拜托
You're smarter than this. Come on!
迪恩说得对
Dean's right.
得先把号角给路西法
Priority is to put the Horn in Lucifer's hands.
让他去对付阿玛拉
and set him loose on Amara.
但要先把路西法从小卡身体里驱逐出去
After we exorcise Lucifer out of Cass.
然后把他放进新皮囊里
and put him into a new vessel.
什么
What?
- 不是吧 - 当然啊
- Really? - Yes, really.
我们不能派路西法穿着小卡上战场
We're not gonna send Lucifer into battle inside Cass.
如果他死了呢
What if he doesn't make it?
迪恩 那是个强大的皮囊
Dean, it's a strong vessel.
他支撑了小卡那么多年
It's held Cass for years,
我们都知道他都经历了多少事
and we know what he's been through.
我猜它也能支撑路西法
I'm guessing it can hold Lucifer.
「它」
"It"?
那不是「它」 萨姆 那是小卡
It's not an "it, " Sam. It's Cass.
是小卡想这么做的
And Cass wanted to do this.
是啊 有时候我还想要戴佐罗面具的女孩
Yeah, well, there's times I want to get slapped during sex.
在做爱时打我呢
by a girl wearing a Zorro mask.
不代表那就是个好主意了
That don't make it a good idea.
迪恩 我们就是这样坑了自己
Dean, this is exactly how we screw ourselves.
我们总做情绪化的选择
W-We make the … the heart choice.
而不是明智的选择
instead of the smart choice.
好吧 菲尔医生 多谢了
Oh, okay. Thank you, Dr. Phil.
小卡是我们的家人
Cass is family.
是的 我们应该尊重他的选择
Yes, and his choice deserves to be respected.
就算他因此而死
Even if it kills him.
你们简直要我命了
It's killing me.
我宁可往眼睛里插一根火热的叉子
I would rather stick white-hot skewers in my eyes.
也不想再听你俩小碎嘴吵了
than listen to you two bitches bicker!
我把条件都说清楚了
I gave you the terms of my deal.
路西法不回笼子
If Lucifer's not back in the Cage,
就别指望拿到号角
the Horn stays hidden.
皮囊恢复得很好
The vessel is healing nicely.
你很快就能重焕精神了
Soon you'll be shipshape and Bristol fashion.
你似乎对我的进展很满意
You seem pleased with my progress.
但我觉得你似乎做不到善良
But I don't sense in you the capacity for kindness.
或关切
or…concern.
善良只能帮你赚到一个拥抱
Kindness gets you a hug,
而不能让你当上重要人物
not a seat at the big boys' table.
你想要什么
And what is it you want?
就像你 我想找路西法复仇
Oh, like yourself, I want revenge on Lucifer.
但不止如此 我想见证你
But more than that, I want to be there.
按自己的意愿重塑世界
when you remake the universe to your taste.
我听说我的意愿更像灾难
I'm told my tastes run towards the catastrophic.
是啊
Aye.
温家兄弟说你最喜欢毁灭了
The Winchesters say you are all about destruction.
温家兄弟说得对
The Winchesters are right.
但是
But…
他们所谓的「毁灭」
what they call "Destruction"
我称之为整修
I call renovation.
按我的计划来 不是上帝的
My blueprints. Not God's.
这就对了
That's my girl.
按你独特的方式来
Do things the way you would have done them.
我会的
I will.
那有你什么事呢
And where do you fit into that?
我可以帮上忙的
Oh, I can be useful.
给你提供
Provide you with information.
麻烦兄弟和路西法的消息
on the troublesome brothers and Lucifer …
以及他们的计划
their plans.
虽然这是出于我的自身利益考虑
And even if it is born out of my own self-interest,
我的确关心你
I … I care about you.
你可以跟我说说话
I'm someone you can talk with.
谈谈心
Confide in.
你有过这样的人吗
Have you … Have you ever had that?
我一直是一个人
I've always been alone.
你不用非得一个人 亲爱的
Oh, you don't have to be, darlin'!
好吧
Well…
不管你在做什么 似乎挺有效
whatever you're doing, it seems to be working.
或许我该试练一下
Maybe I should try a little test.
谢谢 喜欢你的勇气
Thank you. Hey, I like your spunk.
我的组织永远欢迎进取者
There's always room for a go-getter in my organization.
我知道我能指望你
Hey, I know I can count on you.
但你的人呢
But what about your people?
他们也同意 还是我得去施施压
They on board, or we need to do a little wing-twisting?
我得考虑一下
I'll have to think about it.
别考虑太久了
Don't you think about it too long.
你也知道那句俗话 犹豫者
You know what they say … He who hesitates…
碎成渣
disintegrates.
你这样太混了
You know, this is a dick move, Crowley.
就算以你的标准来看
Even for you.
你在不讲理
You're not being reasonable.
我不用讲理 我是国王
I don't have to be reasonable. I'm the king.
你看上去很棒啊 有锻炼吗
You look great. You been working out?
听我怒吼
Hear me!
那是什么
What the hell was that?
知道吗 伙计们 我觉得是她
You know what, fellas? I think that's her.
那
Well, that…
是报复 女士们先生们
was a little payback, ladies and gents.
我觉得阿玛拉姑姑
I don't think Auntie Amara.
不喜欢你们二把刀的袭击
appreciated your little half-assed smiting.
还有 这
And, uh guess what … This …
这只是即将发生的事的一点预告
This is just a teeny taste of what's to come.
显然
So, clearly.
我的专长是能派上用场的
my expertise is gonna come in handy.
因为上帝知道接下来会如何
'Cause God knows what's next.
哎呦
Ouch.
差点忘了
I almost forgot.
上帝不在乎
God doesn't care.
好了
Okay.
我恢复了
I'm back.
好了
Okay.
这下我们都知道她心情不好时
S-So now we all just saw what happens.
会发生什么了
when she's in a bad mood,
显然她从时间之初就一直没高兴过
which, apparently, she's been in since the dawn of time.
我觉得她刚刚动了动小指
I think she just rattled heaven.
就把天堂搅得一团乱
with a flick of her pinkie finger.
你还看不清现实吗
That's not a big enough dose of reality for you?
我们在争什么
Why are we arguing?
我们都知道他得回到笼子里
We all know that he has to go back in the Cage.
是的 等时候到了
Yes, when it makes sense.
阿玛拉是更要紧的
Amara's the big picture here now, okay?
想要干掉她
Look, in order to take her out,
就得把约书亚的号角给路西法
Lucifer has got to have the Horn of Joshua.
他干掉她 我们干掉他
He does her, we do him.
拜托了
Check, please.
怎么样 温家兄弟准备干什么
Well? What are the Winchesters preparing to do?
没什么
Mm, nothing.
吓得不行了
Paralyzed with fear.
他们不知道该做什么
They don't know what to do.
你是对的
You're right.
留着你是挺有用的
You're actually handy to have around.
谢谢
Thanks.
多谢你这么说
Lovely of you to say.
克劳力 时间不多了 你同不同意
Crowley, ticktock. You with us?
你们的论点
The crux of your dispute.
在于路西法
is your contention that Lucifer,
是唯一
and only Lucifer,
能使用号角对付阿玛拉的人 是吧
can use the Horn to beat Amara, right?
没错
You got it.
但只有在你们有
Well, that scenario only works.
那个号角的情况下才行 而你们没有
if you actually possess said Horn, which you do not.
是的 但是你有 所以
No, we don't. But you do, so …
没错 我有
Exactly! I do!
这不是谈判
This isn't a negotiation.
我有王牌 你们有
I have the high cards, and you have …
等等
Hold on. Give me a second.
我看看 一张牌没有
Let me have a look … no cards!
我的提议不变
My offer stands.
我们把路西法从笼子里放出来时
When we sprung Lucifer from the Cage,
我们有罗威娜和《诅咒之书》
we had Rowena and the Book of the Damned.
我们需要这两样
Both of which we will need.
才能把他关回笼子 而两样现在都没了
to put him back in the Cage, both of which are gone.
伙计们
Guys.
你继续说
Back to you.
伙计们
Guys.
看啊
Look at this.
（我死而复生了 费格斯）
我讨厌这样
I hate this.
嗯
Yeah.
对了 克劳力呢
And, by the way, where the hell is Crowley?
我们差不多都布置好了
I mean, we're essentially all set up.
是啊 是他逼我们这么做的
Yeah, I mean, he's the one that boxed us into doing this.
- 他至少也该 - 出现吗
- You'd think he'd have the decency to … - Show up?
他出现了
He does.
因为没有诱饵
Because without the bait,
那么
well…
就不能称之为陷阱了嘛
a trap really isn't a trap, is it?
就是那个吗
That's it?
看上去不怎么特别啊
Doesn't look like much, does it?
第一印象未必是准的 小鹿
First impressions can be deceiving, Moose.
比如 我曾觉得你无聊没劲呢
For instance, I once thought of you as dull and plodding.
算了 这个比喻不好
Oh, never mind. Bad analogy.
告诉你 我们依然觉得这主意不好
For the record, we still think this is a bad idea.
我们应该利用路西法 不是杀了他
We should be using Lucifer, not icing him.
我知道
I'm aware.
如果你犹豫了 我就站这儿
So I'll be standing right here should you hesitate.
施予之手也可以拿走
The hand that giveth can so quickly taketh away.
是啊 我们明白
Yes, we getteth it.
妈妈 你刚刚说到
So, Mummy, you were telling us.
你令人着迷的还魂故事
your fascinating tale of resurrection.
但你没有说
But you never did say exactly.
你这段时间究竟去哪了
where you'd been this whole time.
跟你一样 费格斯 躲起来了
Same as you, Fergus. Hiding.
如果黑暗王子知道我还活着 我就死定了
Once the Dark Prince knew I was alive, I wouldn't be.
这次别像上次那样搞小动作了
No mucking about like last time.
符文和圣火
The warding and the holy fire.
不能关大天使太久
won't keep an archangel but for a moment.
如果他会来的话
If he shows up at all.
他会来的
Oh, he'll show.
他太急着想干掉阿玛拉了
He's too hungry to take Amara out,
而我们又有能干这个的武器
and we've got the blaster to do it.
[咒语]
我召唤你是有东西想给你
I summon you to make an offer.
我有可以用来
The weapon by which its bearer.
永远击溃黑暗的武器
can crush the Darkness forever.
萨姆 快
Sam, now!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你的祈祷暗示我会
Your prayer implied that I'd be…
加入你们
joining the team,
但我怎么感觉不到热情呢
but I'm just not feeling the warm and fuzzy here.
在那儿呢
There it is.
老爸亲自注入了能量
Powered up by Dad himself.
那玩意 加上我
Well, that bad boy plus me …
的确足以干掉她
That ought to take her out all right.
我们开始吧
Let's get to it.
熄灭火焰
Douse the flames.
或者不
Or don't?
小卡
Cass!
卡西迪奥 现身
Castiel, show yourself!
迪恩
Dean?
小卡
Cass.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
怎么回事
What's … What's going on?
小卡 听我说
Cass, listen to me.
我们没多少时间
We don't have a whole lot of time, okay?
你得…
You have got to …
小卡
Cass.
卡西迪奥 现身
Castiel, show yourself!
他得什么
Uh, he's got to what?
你们俩
You boys …
你们刚刚差点套住我了
Ooh, you almost had me there for a minute,
不过这些邮购的咒语
but these mail-order spells …
实在没有吹的那么厉害 是吧
They're just not what they're cracked up to be, are they?
小卡 驱逐他 你得把路西法逐出体内
Cass, expel him! You got to kick Lucifer out!
听到了吗
Do you hear me?!
说实话 我觉得他对这种安排挺满意的
Honestly, I think he's happy with the arrangement.
毕竟是他自己邀请我进来的 迪恩
I mean, he did invite me in and all, Dean.
小卡
Cass!
把武器交出来 怎么样
Hand over the weapon. What do you say?
要不咱们就等这符文失效
Or we can just wait for this warding to fail.
然后我自己来拿
and I'll take it.
该死
Bloody hell.
会没事吗
Is it going to be all right?
会没事的
It's going to be all right!
必须的
Oh, you bet!
亲爱的朋友们 会没事的
Dear friends, it is going to be all right.
今晚会没事的
It's going to be all right tonight.
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
世界已经终结了
The world ended.
克劳力 你怎么来了
Oh, Crowley. What are you doing here?
今天谁生日来着
Uh, say, who was born today?
这是温家的厨房吗
Is this the Winchesters' kitchen?
算是吧
Sort of.
我在脑海里来这里打发时间
I come here in my mind to pass the time.
不知什么原因 这里信号特别好
For some reason, it has excellent reception.
你怎么回事 路西法对你做了什么
What's wrong with you? What has Lucifer done to you?
他基本不怎么搭理我
Well, he mostly just leaves me alone.
我就在这儿等着
I'm just waiting here, you know,
等着跟黑暗开战
for the battle with the Darkness.
他还真给你洗脑了
He's really got his hooks in you.
振作起来
Snap out of it.
你知道外面发生什么了吗
Do you know what's happening out there?
温家兄弟困住了那混蛋
The Winchesters have trapped the abomination.
好让你驱逐他
so that you can expel him.
这样他们就能把他关回笼子里了
so that they can put him back in the Cage.
这主意听着可不怎么样
Well, that doesn't sound like a very good idea.
以你现在的情况 你没资格指手画脚
In your current state, you're in no position to judge.
等等 我刚才看到的是迪恩 是吗
Wait. That was Dean I saw a minute ago, wasn't it?
对
Yes.
他想让我驱逐路西法
And he wants me to expel Lucifer?
是的
Yes!
好吧
Well…
他对现在的情况看法还挺客观的
he may have a more objective view of the situation.
也许我是该驱逐他
Maybe I should.
那就马上动手吧 省的夜长梦多
So, let's do it now before it's too late.
已经太晚了
It already is.
不是吧 克劳力
Really, Crowley?
你想把我关回笼子里
You want to put me back in the Cage?
我是哪里都不会去的 你也是
Well, I'm not going anywhere, and neither are you.
他已经去了好一会儿了
You know, he's been gone a long time.
你觉得现在什么情况
I mean, what do you think is going on?
不知道 也许小卡不愿意合作
I don't know. Maybe Cass isn't willing to play ball.
你自己说过的 他想要这样
I mean, you said it yourself … he wanted this.
你俩就不能干好点什么事吗
Can't you people do anything right?!
在这里磨磨蹭蹭的 我们的时间不多了
Whilst all this dithering goes on, we're losing time!
你们看 符文快要失效了
Look … The warding's beginning to fail.
拜托 小卡 怎么回事啊
Come on, Cass. What the hell?
你个二流会计
You second rate bean counter.
伙计们 你们这样会打坏什么的
Guys, you're gonna break something.
（救我）
你想坐上我的王位
You wanted my throne.
你密谋想篡位取代我
You plotted to replace me!
[咒语]
你以为有野心
As if ambition.
会装腔作势就等于威仪了吗
and posturing were the same as majesty!
[咒语]
地狱里所有人都看不起你
Everyone in hell despises you.
他们完全明白你是个什么东西
and sees you for exactly what you are …
屁都不如
nothing.
[咒语]
克劳力
Crowley.
没用
Useless.
路西法对他的控制太强
Lucifer's hold on him is too strong.
伙计们 火灭了
Lads, the fire!
耍我
Trick me?
骗我
You lied to me.
我本来可以做你们的战士的
You know, I could have been your warrior.
谁需要你们啊
Who needs ya?
克劳力总在派对刚开始的时候离开
It's just like Crowley to leave right when the party's getting started.
坐吧
Have a seat.
尽管我从你俩身上得到了很多乐趣
As much as I get a giggle out of you two, and I do,
每段关系 总有一个…
there comes a time when every relationship has…
到头的时候
run its course.
所以…
So…
路西法
Oh, Lucifer.
亲爱的侄子
Dear nephew,
天呐 你变化真大
my, how you've changed.
她离我而去后 我就开始追踪她
I was tracking her when she left my side.
你本来被封印得好好的
You were safely sealed away.
你会希望自己没被放出来
You're gonna wish you'd stayed there.
我觉得你和我得好好地长谈一次
I think you and I need to have a nice, long chat.
小卡
Cass?
那么 罗威娜和克劳力
So, Rowena and Crowley …
真是有其母必有其子
like mother, like son, huh?
当情况不妙时 他俩真的都是
They both took exactly one split second to take off.
瞬间就跑了
when things started going south.
- 是啊 - 给
- Yep. - Here.
对了 罗威娜跑去阿玛拉那里做什么
By the way, wh-what's Rowena doing with Amara?
我猜 她是想赌一把
My guess … she's playing the odds.
抱路西法的大腿没抱住
When sucking up to Lucifer didn't work out,
也许她觉得把注压在阿玛拉身上胜算最大
maybe she thought Amara was the best bet.
然后她又听说路西法真有机会
Then she heard Lucifer had a shot,
于是又一次倒向了他
so she switched horses again.
我也以为路西法有机会的
I thought Lucifer had a shot.
显然 大天使加上上帝之力
Apparently, uh, archangel plus God power.
并不能打败上帝的妹妹
doesn't trump God sister.
但假如这玩意必须得由上帝的选民来使用
But if the thing has to be used by God's chosen,
那么也许一个被炒鱿鱼的大天使并不够格
then maybe an archangel who got the boot doesn't qualify.
无论如何
Either way,
号角的神力已经被用尽了 所以…
horn's out of ammo, so…
所以我们又回到了起点
So, back to square one.
是啊
Yep.
听着…
Listen, um…
我知道我先前支持
I know I came down on the side.
让小卡去解决阿玛拉 所以…
of wanting Cass to deal with Amara, so …
他自己也是这么想的 不是吗
Well, that's what he wanted, though, right?
再说了 我们不是说好今后
Besides, didn't we say that we were gonna swear off.
当一个人做出另一个人并不赞同的决定时
getting in the way when one person makes a choice.
我们不再干涉吗
the other doesn't agree with?
是啊…
Yeah, um…
没错 我们是说过
Yeah, we did say that.
所以…
So…
好吧
Okay.
这就是我们的政策了
So, that's our policy.
听起来真不错
Which sounds damn good.
我们去找到那个傻瓜带他回家吧
Well, let's go find that idiot and bring him home.
好了
Okay.
我知道你对我有意见
Look, I know you have a major beef with me.
你也许想结果了我
You probably want to finish me.
但你需要考虑你的处境
But you may want to rethink your position.
我可能会对你有帮助
'Cause I could actually be of use to you.
真的
Really?
你没想过
You hadn't considered?
我们都跟上帝有账要算
We both have an ax to grind with God.
我知道他的弱点
I know his soft spots.
他没法同时对付我们两个
He can't handle us both.
你真的觉得我可能会相信你吗
Do you, for one moment, think that I would actually.
不论出于什么理由
consider trusting you for anything?
我相信过你一次
I did trust you once.
你和我哥哥合谋把我封印了那么久
You and my brother conspired to seal me away for eons.
但你说得对
But you're right.
你确实可能对我有些用
You might be of some use to me.
好吧
All right.
很好
Good.
这就对了
Now we're talking.
作为上帝最喜爱的大儿子
As God's favorite, his first son,
你也许是世间万物中唯一一个
you may be the one thing in all of creation.
他仍然在乎的
that he still cares about,
唯一一个能逼他现身的
the one thing that could finally make him show himself?
那样我就可以和他面对面
So that I can confront him.
让他承认他给我的委屈
and he can acknowledge the wrongs he's done me.
然后他就可以
And then he can witness.
在他自己被毁灭前
the utter destruction.
目睹他创造的一切
of all his creation…
灰飞烟灭
before he himself is swept away.
你在等他出现吗
You're expecting him?
别等了
I wouldn't wait up.
我确信他已经搭上了远走高飞的「末班车」
I'm pretty sure he caught the last train out.
好吧
Well…
那就走着瞧了
We'll see, won't we?